hello
Here
is
Howard
note
of
homework2
Homework
1. Create a new branch using last week's repository (or create a new one).
2. Push a new commit to the new branch.
3. Check out the main branch and merge the changes.
4. Use git log + git revert to revert to any previous revision.
• Please take screenshots and briefly describe the process. Output the result as a PDF and submit it to the workspace.
• Please use a terminal (Git Bash, PowerShell, cmd, etc.) for this assignment.